{
    "id": "891e292430004aa3bfaf1a95a215dc18",
    "title": "Direct And Indirect Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The girl said that it ..................................... her great pleasure to be there that evening.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "gives",
                "gave",
                "would give"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The man ........................................... that he must go as soon as possible.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "said",
                "asked",
                "told"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She said that she ........................................... to see any of them and asked them to go away.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did not want",
                "does not want",
                "had not wanted"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher says that if you work hard you .....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will pass",
                "would pass"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He said that he ..........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "won",
                "has won",
                "had won"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He proposed that they ....................................... wait for her return.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shall",
                "will",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Alice exclaimed how clever .........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was she",
                "she was"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The young man asked which way she ........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has gone",
                "had gone",
                "would go"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked me where .................................... going.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I was",
                "was I",
                "I am"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She requested them to wait there till she ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "returns",
                "returned",
                "will return"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}